Saint benefactor listen [Music] Please Lord, I
request you, do not delay the work of the people, I am eager to
give you great happiness, how can you jump over the ocean,
Surasa's body penetrated further,
Lankini was stopped and she overturned, she went to the heavens,
give happiness to Vibhishan, Sita [Music] look at me, take the supreme
position, the garden is deserted, the great ocean is very eager, do it to me,
Akshay Kumar [Music] Kumar
Sanara, spreading the fire around Lanka, let
Lanka burn, Jai Jai [Music] Jai tune, there was an uproar
in the heaven, due to the helplessness, Swami, please bless me,
Jai Jai Laxman, the giver of life, I am
eager, remove the sorrow, Jai Giridhar,
Jai Jai, ocean of happiness, group of surs Samarth Bhatnagar Om Hanu Hanu
Hanumant, hit the enemy [Music] hit the enemy with
thunderbolt, mace, thunderbolt, Maharaj,
save your servant Omkar